各位 Polycasters  大家好
Hey there, Polycasters.
我是 Rob
Rob here.
对于优秀的 Web 应用来说  动画是必不可少的
Animation is one of the hallmarks of a really great web experience.
不仅仅是因为它能让你的应用看上去很炫
Not only does it make your app just look cool.
你还可以利用动画引导用户转向
But you can use them to navigate the user from one
你希望的用户关注的页面
area of interest to the next.
更重要的是动画使得网站的整体效果显得十分引人注目
And ultimately, that makes everything much more engaging.
在之前的一部视频里
Now, in a previous video, I showed you
我为大家展示了如何用动画为单个元素增加效果
how to animate a single item using an animation behavior.
不过今天在这里我会为大家讲解
But today I want to teach you how
如何为整个应用添加动画
to animate whole sections of your app,
将共有的元素从当前状态转向下一个状态
bringing shared elements from one state to the next.
要实现这个目标  我们需要用到一个叫做 Neon-Animated-Pages
And to do this, we're going to use a component called
的元素
Neon Animated Pages.
好吧
OK.
这是我们要实现的第一个模块
So this is the first thing we're going to build.
它是一个特别简单的应用程序
It is a very simple application.
在这个页面中  我们会添加一个设置按钮
And we are going to add a little Settings menu to this page,
当你点击它的时候
so that when you click on it, it's
会产生一些特别漂亮的效果
going to do some really nifty transitions.
它会通过滑动动画切换到另一个页面
It's going to actually slide the other page in.
当你取消它的时候  它会将之前的页面
And when you cancel it, it's going to sort of push
以“推”的方式切换回去
the old page back over.
是吧
Right?
非常棒的效果
So pretty cool stuff there.
在开始之前  我们先来看看工程里的
To start off, we are going to jump into our Index file
Index 文件
for this project.
首先要做的是
And the first thing we're going to do
添加一些 import 代码
is we are just going to load in some imports.
这里我们需要引用 Neon-Animated-Pages
So we're going to pull in Neon Animated Pages as well
把它作为 iron-flex-layout 类
as the iron-flex-layout classes, which we talked about
我们在上一集视频中已经聊过相关的内容  所以这里可以直接使用
in our last episode, so we can use some layout classes.
在我的 body 块的下面
And then down inside of my body, I'm
我要添加一个 dom-bind 模板
going to just drop in a dom-bind template,
这样我就能在这个代码空间中使用数据绑定
so I can use data bindings in this space.
我会在这里添加 neon-animated-pages 元素
I'm going to add a neon-animated-pages element right there.
你会发现我已经提前做了一些工作  并且用到了这里的一些布局类
And you can see that I've also gone ahead and actually applied
所以我的 body 块会使用 flexbox
some of those layout classes, so that my body is using flexbox
过一会大家就会看到
to allow me to, as you'll see in a second,
flexbox 会拉伸 neon-animated-pages 元素
flex the neon-animated-pages element,
这样它就能占满整个屏幕
so it takes up the entire screen.
接下来我会为它添加一个 selected 属性
I'm also going to give it a selected attribute.
这和我们上次在 Iron Pages 中所做的工作一样
And this is just like what we did in our Iron Pages demo
Neon-Animated-Pages 会
last time, where Neon Animated Pages is going
根据当前 selected index 的值来显示当前的子元素
to look at whatever the selected index is and display that child.
如果 selected index 等于 0  那么它会显示第一个子元素
So if the selected index is 0, it's going to display its first child.
如果 index 等于 1  它会显示第二个子元素  以此类推
If it's 1, it'll display the second child, and so on,
就和 Iron Pages 的效果一样
just like Iron Pages does.
所以它为我们提供了一套实现思路的通用框架
So that gives us a little bit of a boilerplate to work from.
在这里为模板添加 ID
I'm going to add an ID to this template,
这样就能在 JavaScript 中关联它
so I can select it down in JavaScript.
然后再添加 script 标签
And then I will write out a little script tag.
然后继续  并调用 querySelector
And just go ahead and querySelector for my app there.
把它的初始值设置为 0
And give it an initial selected value of 0.
这样一来
So this way, Animated Pages is going
Animated Pages 会显示第一个子元素
to try to display its first child.
我们再添加两个子元素
We're going to drop in two more elements--
list-page 和 settings-page
list-page and settings-page.
我们会在这两个元素之间进行
Those are going to be the two elements that we're
转换
going to transition between.
先为它们添加一些 imports
So I'll go add some imports for them.
我们基本弄得差不多了
And then we are pretty much ready to rock.
接下来我们定义一下 list-page 的样式
So let's start by defining what the list page is going to look like.
这样我们就能切换到那个页面
So we can switch over to that tab.
这是特别典型的元素
And it's pretty typical element here.
这里我已经添加了 style 标签和
I've got my style tag and my template tab
template 标签页 不过由于它的代码太多  所以整块代码自动收缩了
collapsed right now, because they're full of just placeholder markup.
如果我把它扩展开  你会看到这里有一大堆 HTML
So if I expand that, you can see there's a bunch of HTML in there.
不过大家不需要担心这些
But you don't actually need to worry about any of that,
在这个演示程序中所涉及到的元素都是特别简单的
because it's all just dummy placeholder content
大家一看即懂
for the sake of the demo.
所以虽然看上去一大堆东西  不过大家可以忽略大部分
So a lot of stuff, but you can pretty much ignore it.
我们继续  这里需要再添加一些引用
To get rolling, though, I'm going to import a few items here.
这里引用 neon-animatable-behavior
I'm going to import the neon-animatable-behavior, which
大家也许还记得在之前 Neon Animation 相关的视频中也讲到过这些
you might remember from our previous episode on Neon Animation.
接下来我会添加两个动画
And then I'm going to pull in two
slide-from-left (从左侧滑入)动画和 fade-out-animation (淡出)动画
animations-- slide-from-left animation and fade-out-animation.
slide-from-left 会使页面
So slide-from-left is going to make
从屏幕左边滑入
the page appear to come from outside the left edge
然后滑到页面中间  就像这样
of the screen onto the center of the page like that.
而 fade-out-animation
And then the fade-out-animation, as it implies,
它会将页面淡出屏幕
is just going to have the page fade out.
我们往下看
So then let us go down here and like we've
和我们之前实现演示应用的过程一样  这里先创建一个属性对象
done in previous animation examples, we'll create a properties object.
这里我们添加一个动画设置属性
We'll create an animation config property.
然后我会为它添加两个动画  一个入场动画
And then I'm going to give it two animations, an entry
一个离场动画
and an exit animation.
我会使用我们引用的动画
And we're going to use those animations that we imported.
所以我们的入场动画就是 slide-from-left
So our entry animation will be slide from left.
而我们的离场动画就是 fade-out
Our exit will be fade out.
还有我们需要记得引用 neon-animation-behavior
We also need to remember to include that neon-animatable-behavior.
如果大家对这个不是特别熟悉
Now, if this does not look familiar to you,
请大家去看一下我们之前的关于 Neon Animation
please, please, please go check out our previous episode
的视频
on Neon Animations.
那部视频中会解释这些‘行为’是如何工作的
That will explain how these behaviors are working
并且帮大家补充一些背景知识
and give you a little bit more context.
不过大家如果对这个比较熟悉
But for those of you who are familiar with this,
那么我们就可以继续了
we can just kind of steam right along.
这里我们已经添加了该行为
So we've added that behavior.
并且所有的动画对象都已经设置好了
We've got our animation object all set up.
所以 list-page 基本上完成了
So the list page is pretty much done.
我觉得应该可以从 settings-page 转向 list-page
I think we're ready to switch over to our settings page.
模板里和标签里都是些特简单的内容
And again, you know, it's full of dummy content
大家懂的
in the template and in the style tag.
所以大家不用关心这里的内容
So nothing that you really need to worry about there just yet.
我们还要实现相同的东西
But we're going to do the same thing.
先引用 neon-animatable-behavior
We're going to import the neon-animatable-behavior
和一对转换动画
and then a couple transitions.
从右侧滑入
Slide from right.
然后向右侧滑出
And then slide right.
从右侧滑入的意思就是
So slide from right means basically
从屏幕的边界外面滑入到屏幕正中央
come from off screen to being on screen.
而向右滑动的意思是东西本身已经在屏幕中了
And slide right means you're already on screen, push off
只是将它滑动到右边
to the right-hand side.
帅吧
Cool?
所以就和我们在 list 页面上所做的一样
So just like we were doing with our list page,
接下来我们会继续实现这里的行为
we're going to go ahead and implement the behavior.
这里我们会用到 neon-animatable
So we're going to roll in neon-animatable.
我们会创建一个属性对象
We're going to create a properties
它带有一个设置属性
object with an animation config property.
包括入场和离场动画
Entry and exit animations.
对于入场动画
And for entry, we're going to say
我觉得我们所期望的效果是
that we want this guy to-- I believe we're going
从右侧滑入
to slide in from the right.
好吧
Yep.
而我们的离场动画  我们让页面从右边出去
And then for our exit, we will slide out to the right.
而这两个动画都会
And both times, the node is just going
引用这个元素本身
to refer to this element itself.
所以我们搞定了页面
So we've got our two pages.
同时与页面相关的动画也准备就绪了
They've got their animations already set up and ready to go.
接下来我们转向浏览器
Let's switch over to the browser.
我们可以先预览一下
We can actually preview this.
而我只需要利用一些开发工具上的小技巧即可
And what I'm going to do is a little dev tools trickery,
大家之前也看到我用过类似的方式
which you've seen me do before.
在开发工具中  我已经在这里选上了 neon-animated-pages
I've got neon-animated-pages selected right here in the dev tools.
同时我也打开了控制台
And I've got my console open.
当我点击 $0 的时候
So I can just hit $0, and that will actually
它会帮我捕捉与 neon-animated-pages 相关的元素的引用
allow me to grab a reference to the neon-animated-pages element.
所以我可以将所选的内容作为固定的值写在代码里
And I can just set selected to a hard-coded value.
然后将它设置为 1
So I'll just switch it to 1.
大家可以看到它的效果
And you'll see what happens.
页面变化了
The page changes.
当我把它变会 0 的时候
I switch it back to 0.
页面回来了  对吧
The page goes back, right?
设置为 1
Set it to 1.
页面变化
Page changes.
设置回 0  页面回来
Back to 0, page goes back.
现在  我们在页面的转换中加入了非常酷的动画
Now, we've got this really cool relationship between these animations.
你可以看出前后动画的衔接
You can see how they sort of play off
在一些移动设备上
of one another, which looks really nice on perhaps
会显得特别棒
a mobile device of some kind.
手动修改这个值
It is a little bit of a bummer, though,
显然是有点懒人风格的做法
to have to manually change the selected value in this way.
我们来修改一下
So let's fix that.
这里我们需要做的是
And what we're going to do is we're
让我们的元素能够分发事件
going to have our elements dispatch events.
当我们收到这些事件的时候就通知切换动画元素
When we hear those events, we'll tell the animated pages element
更新页面
to update.
所以我们可以在这个模板中添加实现代码
So we can actually pop inside of the template there.
这里我要利用一下 Settings 按钮
And I'm going to take the Settings button
在它里面加入 on-tap handler  和 showSettings 方法
and just give it an on-tap handler and a method called showSettings.
要实现我们的目标  这里只要触发一个叫做 showSettings 的事件
And then to implement that, I'm just going to fire an event
即可
called showSettings.
然后在 Settings 页面里实现相同的事
I'll do the exact same thing on the Settings page.
这回针对 Cancel 按钮  还有添加另外一个 on-tap handler
I'll find its Cancel button, another on-tap handler.
这里我们称它为 showList
This time we'll say showList.
我们再实现另外一个事件
And we'll do another event.
也就是 dispatcher
Dispatcher basically.
所以我们这里会触发另外一个叫做 showList 的事件
So we're just going to fire off another event called showList.
然后在我们的 Index 页面
And then back in our Index page, this
这回我们会快速并且简单地实现它
is going to be a little quick and dirty.
不过这里我打算
But what I'm going to do is I'll just
仅仅在文档级别上监听这些事件
listen at the document level for those events.
一般来讲  你所需要的就是 neon-animated-pages
So normally, you would probably have this neon-animated-pages
和这些元素
and these elements.
也许你有一个更加庞大的元素
You'd probably have this inside of maybe,
里面包含了这些东西
like, a bigger element of some kind.
你可以用 on-dash listener 来监听这些东西
So you could use, like, on-dash listeners to listen to these things.
比如说你想要监听 on-show-settings
You'd be like, oh, yeah, I want to listen to on-show-settings.
当我接收到它的时候  我会更新 selected 属性
And when I hear that, that's when I'll update my selected property.
由于我们这里仅仅为大家提供一个示例
In this case, we're just doing a quick little demo here,
所以我在这里只是在文件中进行监听
so we'll just listen right on the document.
搞定这些以后  我们基本上差不多了
With that in place, I think we're actually good.
返回到 Chrome
We can switch back to Chrome.
当我们点击按钮的时候
And then when we click our little button up there,
它会启动事件
it's going to fire the event, which
该事件会触发动画页面的更新
is going to trigger a change in animated pages.
然后我们来点击以下 Cancel 按钮
And we'll click that Cancel button.
同样的
And likewise.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
如果你希望所有的页面
Now, if you want all of your pages
都具有相同的转化效果
to use the same transitions, it would
那么你就得把这段代码一次又一次复制粘贴
be really inconvenient to have to copy and paste that code
太不方便了
over and over and over again.
不过还好  我们可以通过把它
But thankfully, we can work around that using
内建到元素内部来避免反复复制粘贴
a feature that's built into the element itself.
好吧
OK.
而在我们的第二个 demo 中  我这里有一个特别简单的转换动画
For our second demo, I've got this very simple transition thing.
每一个都是一个页面
Each one of these is a page.
每个颜色块都是一个页面
Each one of these big colored blocks is actually a page.
而当我点击的时候  你可以看到
And as I'm clicking, you can see that they all
他们都使用了同一个转换动画
use the exact same transition animation.
我们来看一下代码  它看上去和我们的之前的示例一样
So looking at our code, it looks just like our old example.
这里我们已经有一个 neon-animated-pages 元素了
We've got a neon-animated-pages element here.
对吧
Right?
我们还用到一些布局类
We're using some layout classes.
现在来优化一下
We're flexing it.
这里有一个与已选数据相关的数据集
We've got a selected binding right there.
在下一个方法中我会得到一个 handler
And then I've got this little handler
添加它主要为了给大家演示
that I've added just for demo purposes
这个 handler 叫 on-tap  里面引用了这个“next”方法
called on-tap, where I've got this next method.
这里我会遍历一下已选的数据
And I'm just looping through possible selected values.
这里会一直递增直到最大值为止
So we're incrementing up until we reach the max.
然后返回来再循环
And then we're looping around again.
大家可以看到我这里的元素都是一样的 对吧
Now, I've got the same element in each of these slots, right?
而我希望能够通过相同的转换方法
And I know that I'm going to want all of these
处理这些数据
to use the same transition.
即使我们这里没有相同的元素
Even if I didn't have the same element here,
我仍然希望能够使用相同的转化方法来处理他们
maybe I would want all of them to use the same transition.
所以与其单独处理每一个数据
So instead of having to go into each and every one and copy
将行为一遍又一遍地复制黏贴
and paste that behavior over and over again,
我这里可以利用
what I'm going to do is just take advantage
动画页面所提供的一个特性
of this convenience feature that animated-pages offers,
首先回到代码顶部
where I can go up to the top, and I can just
在这里引用我想要使用的动画
import the animations that I want it to use,
就好像我们之前构造动画元素一样
as if we were building an animatable element.
不过这里我仅仅使用放大动画和淡出动画
But I'll just pull in a scale-up animation and a fade-out animation.
然后我们会通知动画页面
And then we're just going to tell animated pages,
对于入场动画
hey, for all of your entry animations,
只需要播放放大动画即可
just play the scale-up animation for all of these.
无所谓它的内容是什么
It doesn't matter what it is.
就播放它吧
Just play that.
而对于所有的离场动画  仅播放淡出动画
And for all the exit animations, just play the fade-out animation.
所以如果你希望所有的页面
So if you know you want all of your pages
都使用相同的入场和离场动画
to use the exact same intro and exit animations,
这是一个便捷的方式
this is some shorthand that you can
它能帮你省掉不少时间
do that will save you quite a lot of typing if you have
而且适用于不同元素共享相同动画
a bunch of different elements that all basically
的应用场景下
need the same transitions.
所以有了它  一切都搞定了
So with this in place, we're actually pretty good to go.
我们打开浏览器  点击一下试试
We can switch back to the browser and click on the thing.
效果差不多
And we're going to get that exact same behavior.
确实省了我们不少时间
And it's saved us quite a lot of typing.
最后我想要实现的是
Now, the last thing that I want to touch on
我在视频开头所提到的
is something that I promised at the beginning of the video--
可以将元素从一个页面传递到下一个页面
this idea of being able to take elements and transition them
还记得吧
from one page to the next, right?
其实也就是利用 neon-animated-pages
Actually pulling along what neon-animated-pages
内部的 shared elements (共享元素)
refers to as shared elements.
那么我来为大家举个例子
So let me show you an example of doing that.
这里有一个比较简单的应用
I've got a very simple app here.
这里有一个“登入”按钮
And it's got this sort of large Sign In button of sorts.
当我点击“登入”按钮的时候
And when I go click on that Sign In button,
你可以看到它在进行切换
you'll see that it's going to transition
并成为我下一个页面的顶部
and become the header of my next page.
我们再重新做一遍
So let's do that again, right?
我已经得到了那个元素
So I've actually taken that element,
然后把它变换成另一个页面的一个元素
and sort of morphed it into an element on another page,
然后将这个元素从页面一转移到页面二
and sort of carried it from page one to page two.
这个就是共享元素的转换
So again, this is a shared element transition.
特别是这里  这个叫做 hero transition
And in particular, this one is called a hero transition
或者 hero animation
or a hero animation.
实现这个特别简单
So implementing this is actually pretty easy.
虽然这些效果看上去特别复杂
Though the effects themselves look very sophisticated,
当大家知道原理以后  就知道其实实现起来挺简单的
they're pretty easy to implement once you know how.
而在我的主页  就像之前的示例
So in my Index page, again, just like the previous examples,
我们已经有了 neon-animated-pages  对吧
I've got neon-animated-pages, right?
我来改改
I'm flexing it.
这里有已选的数据
It's got the selected binding there.
用 next 方法的 handler 来切换页面
We're using a little cheating next handler to advance the page.
这里有两个元素
And I've got two elements inside of here.
一个叫做 main-page  但其实我应该
One is called main-page, though maybe I should
叫它 sign-in-page
have called that sign-in-page.
暂且 main-page
But main-page.
还有 detail-page  它将会是页面的顶部
And detail-page, which is going to be the page with the header.
所以这是我们的主页面
So this is our main page.
我希望大家注意到
And I want you to notice that we've
这里我们有一个 id 为 circle 的 div 标签
got this div with an ID of circle here.
这点非常非常重要
So this is really, really important.
我们之后会再研究这里
And we're going to come back to this later.
现在只要记住它在这个页面里就行了
But just know that it exists inside of this page.
在我们要实现它之前  先回到最上面检查一下
And before we do anything, I'm going to go up and check out
引用
our imports.
与 neon-animatable-behavior 稍有区别
So instead of the neon-animatable-behavior,
这里我们用到了一个和它类似
I've actually got this thing which
不过有一个更长的名字
is very similar, though an even longer name,
叫做 neon-shared-element-animatable-behavior
called neon shared element animatable behavior.
它实现了与 neon-animatable-behavior
So this actually implements all the same stuff
相类似的东西
as the neon-animatable-behavior.
不过它还提供了共享元素
But it gives us this magical shared element
我们接下来会用到这个特性
extra awesome sauce, which we will use in just a second.
这里我有两个动画
And then I've got two animations that I
hero-animation 和 fade-out-animation
pulled in here-- hero-animation and fade-out-animation.
接下来把他们实现了
So let's implement both of those right now.
我们到代码下部
So we'll go down and just like we've
按照我们之前做的那样来实现  我们会将这个行为添加到元素中
done in previous examples, we will add the behavior to our element.
这次  我们会添加 neon-shared-element
So this time, we're going to add the neon shared element
animatable-behavior
animatable behavior.
我们会创建一个属性对象
We will create a properties object.
在这个属性对象中
And in that properties object, we
我们会传入一个设置对象
will drop in an animation config object.
这里我们添加入场和离场动画
We'll have entry and exit animations.
入场动画不是特别重要
The entry animation doesn't really matter,
因为我们不会在这个例子里用到它
because we're not going to play it in this example,
这里我们只是把它放这里而已
but I'll just throw one in there.
而离场动画  请注意这里
The exit animation, though-- pay attention here--
这里我实际上创建了一组动画
I'm actually creating an array of animations-- so animations
所以这些动画应该同时播放
that would be playing simultaneously.
第一个动画应该是 hero-animation
The first one is going to be that hero-animation.
现在我们给它赋一个 ID 属性
And we're going to give it an ID property.
这里我们的目的是希望将 hero-animation 添加到
And we're going to say that we want to hero-animate
id 为 hero 的元素  让它动起来
a thing with the idea of hero.
这里引用的不是 CSS 里的 ID  开始的时候我也搞错了
And this does not refer to a CSS ID, which confused me at first.
记住这个不是 CSS 的 ID
So this is not a CSS ID.
我们将在 JavaScript 中定义这个 ID
This is an ID that we are going to define in JavaScript.
暂时记住我们接下来要定义它
So kind of keep that in mind for the moment.
然后要说的是这里的页面是起始页面
And then we're going to say that this page right here
也就是说我们所引用的 hero 元素
is the from page, meaning that this hero element that we're
将来自于这个页面
going to refer to is coming from this page,
然后它会转向另外一个页面  当我们后面进行实现的时候
and it's going to another page, which we will demonstrate when
会实现下一个元素
we implement the next element.
然后我们要实现
And then we're going to implement
第二个动画  也就是淡出动画
a second animation, which is just going to be fade-out.
简单地说呢
And we're going to basically say,
就是当我们退出的时候  这个页面里的所有元素都会淡出
everything else on this page should fade out when we're exiting.
那么我们来定义一下这个 ID
So let's go define this hero ID thing.
而我们要实现它的关键点就是这个
And the way we're going to do that is through this shared
共享元素对象
elements object.
所以请记住  我在上面这里已经有一个 circle 了
So remember, I've got this circle up here,
没错  就是这个 id 为 circle 的东西
right, this thing with ID of circle.
而它就是我希望进行 " hero 动画" 的目标
And that's really what I want to hero-transition.
所以这里我将添加这个共享元素对象
So I'm going to add this shared elements object.
而且我会告诉它
And I'm going to tell it-- by the way,
顺便说一下  它看上去很像我们的动画设置对象
it looks a lot like our animation config object.
这个值可以将对象与方法相关联
It's a value that turns a function [INAUDIBLE] an object.
不过我要说的是当我们提到“主角”的时候
But we're going to say that when we say hero,
我们真正所指的是这个 .$circle
what we're actually talking about is this .$circle.
而我们这样做的原因是
And the reason why we do this is because this term
因为它会同时在两个元素中被用到  起始页面和终点页面
is going to be used in both elements-- the from page and the to page.
所以它是一个共享的内容  在不同页面中
So it's a shared term referring to different things
引用不同的对象
on different pages.
那么这里  hero 指的是这个 circle
So here, hero refers to that circle.
接下来我们来实现 下一个页面  详细内容页面
Let's go implement the next page, the detail page.
大家可以看到  这里我们添加了相同的引用代码
And you'll see that we've got the same imports pretty much.
我们添加了 shared-element hero-animation fade-out-animation  fade-in
We've got shared-element, hero-animation, fade-out-animation, fade-in.
我们还要实现我们的行为
We're going to also implement our behavior.
这里我们要添加一个动画设置对象
We're going to drop in an animation config object.
而离场动画并不是很重要
And for the exit animation, doesn't really matter,
因为我们并不打算播放离场动画
because we're not going to play one.
这里我简单添加一个离场动画
But I'll just add an exit animation.
这里我们再回到入场动画
But here we are again with the entry animation.
重申一下  它是一个动画队列
Again, it's an array of animations.
并且记住我们使用的是 hero-animation
And note that we're using the hero animation.
这里我们所引用的 ID 也是 hero
The ID that we're referring to is still hero.
不过这里我们要说的是它是目的页面
But now we're saying that this is the to page.
所以第一个元素是起始页面
So the first element was the from page.
而这个目的页面就是 hero 要去的地方
This is the to page where hero is going to.
而对于页面里的其他内容
And then for the rest of the content on the page,
当我们进入页面的时候就让他们淡入即可
we're just going to fade it in when we're doing entry.
然后我们要定义它的共享元素对象
And then we're going to go define its shared elements object.
而这里我们要说的是
And what we're going to say here is
当我们谈到这个元素的 hero 的时候
that when we say hero in this element,
我们实际上所指的是 id 为 header 的元素  对吧
we're referring to our element with the ID of header, right?
所以另外一个 hero 所指的是 circle
So hero in the other one refers to circle.
这里的 hero 指的是我们的 header
Hero over here refers to our header.
而 hero 的引用取决于 neon-animated-pages
And it is up to neon-animated-pages now
也和 hero-animation-behavior 相关
and it is up to that hero animation behavior
把我们的 hero 元素插入到 A 和 B 之间
to sort of interpolate between A and B,
对吧  让我们从那里转到这里
right, to get us from there to here.
对吧
Right?
那么我们继续  试一下
So let's go and give that a shot.
我们回到浏览器  点击以下圆圈
We will go back to our browser and click on our circle.
大家可以看到我们在页面头部上添加了很棒的转换动画
And you see we get that nice transition over to our header.
对于这种设计模式来说  这是一个非常简单的实现
Now, this is a pretty simple implementation of this pattern
而且它的效果很棒
though it is a really cool effect.
不过我希望告诉大家的是
But what I'd like to show you is if you go over
如果到 elements.polymerproject.org 看一下 Elements 页面
to the Elements catalog at elements.polymerproject.org.
在那里点击一下下面的 Neon Animation 按钮
And you click on this Neon Animation button down here,
那里有一个特别棒的指导文档
there is this really awesome guide
有很多关于 Neon Animation 的内容
full of really helpful stuff on Neon Animations.
而在页面的最后  有很多很好的示例
But at the bottom, there are all of these really great demos.
特别提一下  我今天所实现的例子的原型
And one in particular, which I sort of based this on,
我记得好像叫 Squares to Circles 或者
is this one called, like, Squares to Circles or Circles
Circles to Squares 之类的
to Squares, I think.
而且它比之前我为大家展示的
And it is a much more advanced implementation
更加完整  所有这些圆圈
of what I just showed you, where all of these circles
都是动态的 hero-transition  效果非常棒
are actually dynamic hero transitions, which is really cool.
不过它涉及到更多的代码
But it involves a fair bit more code.
所以当你觉得你已经理解了 hero animation 的时候
So once you feel like you understand the original hero
去看看这个例子
animation, go check this one out.
去看看它的效果  然后看看它的实现方法
Go try it out and see how you do.
不过现在大家已经知道了实现的方法
But now you know everything that you
可以在你的 Polymer 应用中构建一些
need to start creating some really, really sick animations
非常非常牛叉的动画
in your Polymer apps.
所以下一次当你希望在应用中
So the next time you want to add a really fancy animation
添加一个很棒的动画的时候 你可以说
to your application, you can just say,
矮油！ 好像有个元素可以搞定它！
hey, there's an element for that.
如果大家喜欢这个视频  请到最下方
Now, if you've enjoyed this video, be sure to go down
点击一下订阅按钮
and click that little Subscribe button.
大家的鼓励才是我们继续努力的动力
That's actually how we get to keep making these.
如果大家有什么疑问  可以在下面的讨论区
And if you have questions, you can leave them for me
给我留言
down in the comments.
或者在社交网站的 #AskPolymer 话题中和我单聊
Or hit me up on a social network of your choosing at #AskPolymer.
同样的  非常感谢大家观看  下次再见
As always, thank you so much for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[MUSIC PLAYING]